A new hero unleashed.
101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure is a family,
animation, adventure film directed by Brian Smith.
Being one of 101 takes its toll on Patch, who doesn't feel unique.
When he's accidentally left behind on moving day, he meets his idol,
Thunderbolt, who enlists him on a publicity campaign.
Thunderbolt (voice), played by Barry Bostwick.
Lightning (voice), played by Jason Alexander.
Lars (voice), played by Martin Short.
Patch (voice), played by Bobby Lockwood.
Cruella (voice), played by Susanne Blakeslee.
Pongo (voice), played by Samuel West.
101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure is a 2003 American animated direct-to-video adventure comedy film
produced by Walt Disney Television Animation with distribution by Walt Disney Home Entertainment.
It serves as the sequel to Disney's 1961 animated
feature film One Hundred and One Dalmatians.
It was directed by Jim Kammerud and Brian Smith, with them also writing the
screenplay from a story by Kammerud, Dan Root, Garrett K.
Schiff, Smith and Temple Mathews and produced by Carolyn Bates and Leslie Hough.
It was released on VHS and DVD on January 21, 2003, and features the voices of Bobby Lockwood, Barry Bostwick,
Martin Short, Jason Alexander, Susanne Blakeslee, Kath Soucie, Jeff Bennett, and Jim Cummings.
The main focus of the sequel is Patch, the loneliest of
puppies, feeling "lost in a sea of spots".
After he gets left behind during the Radcliffe family's moving day, he encounters
his TV hero, Thunderbolt, who enlists him on a publicity campaign.
Critical reception was positive.
The film explores themes of london, england, cartoon, sequel, puppy, dog.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.